Long ago, Gold Roger,
the King of Pirates, obtained
everything the world had to offer,
and his dying roads drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
And thus a new age began.
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
Oh, I'm done playing
through with the waiting,
either will I'm feeling alive,
look out below, wake up sunshine,
here we go.
Raise your flag up high,
hail a brand new dawn.
Blaze across the sky, time
to journey on, on your mark.
Come aboard with me.
We're on Earth, a legendary!.
If you can show your breath?
Then we'll make some waves.
We run our daunted.
Ain't no beginners!
Cause if you're wanted,
Then you're a winner.
For we are on the cruise!
And freedom is the only rule.
Fearless night and day!
Cause that's just our way.
Find one piece!
I'll be the first.
I've heard it be so bad just at first.
It's all this real.
It must be cause my hand's on a wheel.
I'm done playing, feel it's waiting.
In the world I'm feeling alive.
But I'll be loud!
Wake up sunshine, here we go!
We have come so far.
Gotta make it to the end!
Whatever danger we find,
no one ever left behind.
I've always got your back, my friend.
Sail on shoreward, keep marching forward.
Dreaming from the very
first day I'd make my name.
And don't you know that
dream hasn't changed.
I'm done playing through with the wave.
In the world I'm feeling
alive, look out below.
Wake up, sunshine.
Wake up, sunshine, here we go.
We go?
Sorrow!
How did a human cut down
one of us in the water?
And not just any fish man but Heart?
Where does that power come from?
Move it and surround him.
Take an energy steroid just to be sure.
You're screwed now!
Kill them all!
Neptune's army too!
You're good!
What's happening?
It's as if a wave of
madness Has washed over.
Damn it!
Ignore him for now!
Kill everyone else!
Zoro!
Soon the room will be
completely submerged.
Come here and hold on so
that we may flee together.
Hmm, there's something
unnatural about their strength.
My army is highly skilled and
they've made quick work of them.
I have to save my men and
I have to save my kingdom.
Here, you should be able to
secure some air with this.
Oh, good, thanks!
Hang on to me tightly.
This may get rough.
You got it!
There's no more time to spare.
Zoro, swim faster!
We gotta get out of here!
I only hope that my back doesn't
give out when I need it most.
Ready yourselves, my soldiers.
I shall create a path for you.
We shall retreat to fight another day.
Merman. Combat!
Take this!
You're gonna need it!
Here we go.
Neptune's up to something.
Get ready!
Thoreau!
Ultramarine!
All soldiers forward! Sir!
Ride the current and retreat
from the palace! Damn it!
I didn't think they'd pull back!
Now what?
Here, take one of these, boss.
That'll fix you right up.
Don't look back.
We're almost there.
Pass through the gate and head inland.
We gotta move, old man.
Pull it together.
Surely there is nothing
so terrible as old age.
My will is strong, but my
body will not budge an inch.
Not now!
The king is injured.
Your highness.
Hoey.
We're saved!
I owe you my life, Hoey.
Oh, darn it all!
I can't even turn my head.
You're not that old.
Well done, Hoey.
Now come join us and hurry!
Faster!
Don't get a press out.
What's wrong now?
Hmm?
Did we get snagged on
something back there?
Oh, no! Your Highness!
Already grabbed him.
He can't pull away.
The pirates aren't fleeing either.
I thought that swordsman
took care of him already.
Why the hell is he giving
us so much trouble?
Minister, let's go back.
At this rate, the king could be killed.
I told you to retreat, didn't I?
All is not lost if you escape.
Bring my sons and we may see victory yet.
There's no time.
Do as our lord commands.
Both are getting away.
Should we go after them?
Let them run. What do we care?
Soldiers who can't protect
their king are no threat to us.
Speaking of the king, tie him up
in case he gets his strength back.
I have failed you this time, but so long
as my allies live, the battle is not over.
What's that? Don't know.
Maybe the water washed in an old corpse?
So this is the sea forest, huh?
I see why you wanted to come here.
Thank you.
I've wanted to see this place for so long.
You have no idea how much this means.
Hopefully we can get some
peace and quiet here.
Mermaids, ooh!
Oh, man.
Look, it's a Sunny!
Hey, you're right!
And I see Franky, too!
Hey, what's up?
I didn't know you were here!
Cool place, huh?
Wow, look who it is!
Whoa, is that your new girlfriend?
You always did like to aim big!
Let me introduce you.
This here is Crybaby.
Doesn't look like a crybaby to me.
Tell me, sister, do you
live up to your name?
Maybe a little bit.
You may call me Shirahoshi if you please.
So, uh, you're the only
one here? Afraid so.
Robin stopped by earlier, but she
had some Robin business to attend to.
She went to that big
forest of coral over there.
Who knows when she'll be back.
Luffy
It's Jimbae! Awesome!
You're here too!
I'm so pleased that you made it.
You've grown even stronger
than before I can tell.
People said you couldn't come to town so
I was afraid I wouldn't get to see you.
I thought you came here because
you received my message?
Huh? What message?
I didn't hear anything. Hmm.
Most peculiar.
A pleasure to see you, Dean Bay.
It's been ever so long. Yes.
What an unexpected meeting.
But a welcome one.
To what do I owe the...
What are you doing here?
Shouldn't you be in the palace?
Do you have a sec, Franky?
I need some help getting Sanji
and Hachi off this shark.
You got it.
Whoa.
It's the octopus guy.
You...
Looks like you took a beating, brother.
Archie! What?
You're injured.
What happened?
Scratch that.
What are you doing on Fishman Island?
I heard that Arlong was captured, so
I assumed you were as well. You...
Long story.
Maybe later.
Franky!
Let's get Sanji, too!
That's all right.
I'm feeling better.
The mermaid princess at last.
Standing here, I see how
inadequate my imagination was.
Even with all the colors in my arms, I could
never paint a picture as lovely as you.
Uh-huh, no blood loss.
He's being annoying,
but also sort of cool.
The old Sanji is back.
Alas, such beauty as yours is
too fast to fit on any canvas.
Every shade in the world
is reduced to gray.
I don't get it, but who cares?
It's a magical!
Is something wrong?
You're so noisy. Huh?
What is Princess Shirahoshi doing here?
Hey, who the hell is that guy?
That's my ship, buddy! Get off!
Don't flip out, Captain.
This guy's a shipwright.
Tom's brother, actually.
His name's Den.
He's doing the recoding.
Oh, then why didn't you just say so?
He lives in the den and he's
recoding your brother for you, huh?
Sure.
Close enough, I guess.
I mean no disrespect, Princess.
I know why you would come here, but...
Again?
Didn't I kick his ass hard enough?
How many of these is he going to throw?
Get over it, man. What a mess.
What were you thinking, Luffy?
The princess could have been killed.
Come on, have a little faith.
She's got me to save her.
Yep.
She's not scared.
So that's the grave she
wanted to see so bad?
She's been at this an awful long time.
That is her mother's grave.
A monument to Queen Otohime.
Vanderdecken's relentless pursuit began
right after the death of the queen.
Shirahoshi was denied
any chance at closure.
And even worse, she was unable
to attend her mother's funeral.
She spent every day since
locked in the hardshell tower.
I'm sure that over the
years All the things she
wanted to tell her mother
Kept piling up in her heart?
Luffy!
Luffy-chan!
Nami! Kuma!
Oh
Princess Hirohoshi is here too?
Hey!
You ever have that banquet, or what?
No, this one!
He's okay now.
Hatchan!
What in the world happened?
Uh, Kuma...
Hardy did this?
So that's what it's come to.
To think that they were even
able to infiltrate the palace,
this is a dire situation indeed.
What about everyone else
they're not hurt are
they i hope not but let's
hurry back just in case.
Things got worse my father
no how could they do
such a thing to him to
such a kind and gentle man.
I failed you luffy i left you that message
to avoid a fight like
this i didn't want to
get You dragged into
our struggles yet here
we are it's even worse than i ever feared.
We must make haste but humor me for
a moment there is something i should
have told luffy two Years ago when
we first met though it means even
more now i owe a debt of gratitude to
the people Who stopped our long from
running wild in the east blue he had
done more than enough harm already.
I understand that it
was you who defeated him
so i express a long
overdue thank you for that.
And though it pains me i must apologize
as well don't say it 11 years ago Our lung
was locked away by the government and
even knowing what evils he was capable of
I freed him.
Oh, my God.
But what about King
Neptune? Don't look back.
The king's giving us a chance
to make it out of here.
The exit!
We made it outside!
Activate the coral!
That didn't go well at all.
Few guards have skipped.
King Neptune sacrificed himself.
And we have nothing to show from it.
We failed.
Oh, quit their whining.
We followed his orders plain and simple.
Listen up.
This is by no means a repeat.
We'll save the king, take
back the Ryugu palace.
And eradicate that
pirate scum in due time.
But first off.
We need to contact Prince Spook
of Oshie and his brothers.
Find the princess as soon as you can.
Got it?
After that, we'll start regrouping.
And make our way back to the palace.
Hey, we're down the closest
to where we are now.
Fishfurley Hills, sir.
Look out!
Meanwhile, in the high-class
district of Fishfurley Hills.
Get away!
Get in the line now.
You'll do it if you know
what's good for you.
I don't understand.
What do you want from us? Stomp it. What?
It's a test. But why?
Do as we say.
It won't be long before
Horde rules this country.
Now, step on the picture.
But you can't do that.
Yes, you can.
At Candy Factory Town in the Northeast.
Come on, put your foot down.
I can't.
I won't do it.
I can't tread on her image.
I beg you to understand.
Shut up.
Those who will follow our orders will
be branded as human sympathizers.
Which means you'll also
be your enemy in the
southeast outside the
fish man culture hall?
I'll make it easy for you step on the
pitcher or get ready to leave the island.
It's your choice.
That ain't happening
Come on guys
This guy can't be that tough!
Just step on the pitcher.
Anyone who doesn't wanna...
...is gonna get sliced up real good.
At the Marine shopping mall in the East.
What do you mean, leave the country?
This is our home!
We can't leave!
No other place on the
sea floor gets light!
Besides, you're fishmen too.
What makes you think
humans will accept us?
See?
You already know how easily
humans will discriminate
against anything that's
different from them.
Hey, what in the heck is
happening to you, man?
He's being choked!
There's no way that humans and
fishmen will ever coexist peacefully.
Your best bet is to accept
the rule of boarding.
Under his reign, we'll have
the power to change history.
At Waterwheeltown in the north.
Hey, I think it's your
turn. It'll be easy.
I can't do it!
You still haven't stepped on it yet?
Then what good are you?
Hey, aren't you... Fukaboshi?
What is the meaning of this?
Explain yourself!
You scum, how dare you!
Forcing people to tread on
the image of my late mother!
At Coral Hill, after the departure
of Luffy and the others...
It's too late!
There's nothing we can do!
You're right, we let Vanderdekin escape.
And before that,
we couldn't stop the Straw Hats
from kidnapping Princess Shirahoshi.
Didn't the princess say she'd
be back home in time for dinner?
Fool!
They made her say that so we
wouldn't chase after them.
There's a group from the Fishman District
that's terrorizing the entire island.
Seriously?
Well, did they say what's
happening over there?
This is unbelievable.
They said that mermaids are
being reported missing all over.
Princess Shura Hachi.
They wouldn't sell her to the
Celestial Dragons, would they?
Hey, awful news.
It looks like another mermaid
girl just went missing.
This can't be happening.
Form a search party!
Got another one.
Who knew it would be this easy?
Even so, I've just got to
get my hands on that one.
She's the biggest mermaid I've ever seen.
If a human-sized mermaid
can net me 70 million,
then a mermaid that's ten times that size
is bound to bring in an even greater haul.
It's a mermaid motherlode.
Any way you slice it, I'll make a fortune.
Who are you?
Why, hello.
Let me introduce myself
please
princess do not worry Heart
may have seized control of
the palace but King Neptune
will not give in so easily
your father is tougher than you
realize I do still I will help
save the king at any cost Oh,
well, thank you, Team Bay.
I'll be counting on you.
Now, please excuse me.
I have a matter to discuss
with Luffy and his crew.
Beautiful ladies.
Please have some tea.
Whatever, just leave it
over there for right now.
Yeah, you've bothered us enough already.
We're having a serious talk.
You're so sexy when you're
stirred with me, Nami!
Sanchi-Chan hasn't changed one bit.
Mmm, good.
Idiot, that's not for you!
Give it back!
All right, Jinbei.
Let's settle this.
Tell me, what did you mean?
Earlier, you said you set
Arlong loose into the East Blue.
You?
Jinbei, wait!
It's fine.
I heard the same thing. What?
Yeah, a while back,
when Luffy and I first learned
about Jinbei of the Seven Warlords,
Yosaku told us about the
bargain that Jinbei struck.
He's a warlord.
In exchange for becoming one of the Seven,
Jinbei let a dangerous fish
man run wild in the East Blue.
Ah, is that what he told us?
Surprise, surprise.
You didn't remember.
I wonder how Yosaku is doing now.
Two years ago, when I read about you
associating with Jinbei in the newspaper,
However, I honestly didn't
know what to think about it.
I thought Jinbei had been
the key figure pulling
Arlong's strings and
telling him what to do.
So, Jinbei,
I'll give you a chance to defend what
happened, but choose your words wisely.
After all,
our very own navigator here had her entire
life ruined thanks to your buddy Arlong.
To put it simply, whatever you did
turned her world into a living hell.
Depending on what you have to
say, I might not forgive you.
Careful, Hedgen!
Don't move too much!
Your wounds could open up again!
But he's right!
We caused her so much grief!
It's horrible.
And all the apologizing in the
world won't change a thing.
I'm going to guide ships around
all the oceans of the world.
It'll be great!
And then, I can make maps of
all the furthest places I'll go.
This map's the first step
to realizing your dream.
Is that about right? Yep.
Nami, Nojiko, none of
us are actually related.
But that doesn't mean we're not a family.
Really? Pirates!
Pirates are coming!
Everybody run!
Greetings and salutations,
you pathetic little humans!
This village is now mine! Now wait!
Yes!
Better yet, I'll take this whole island!
100,000 fairies for adults,
and 50,000 for children.
Those who cannot pay, die.
It's okay.
Enough, Jitsad.
Now get ready to die.
Nojiko! Nami!
Love you.
What's this?
A map, huh? No!
That's my map!
I drew it and you can't have it!
A child drew this? Look at that! Abby, no!
I'm impressed. Good job.
She could be useful.
Bring her with us.
Right.
Stop!
Let go of me! Stop!
Somebody please help me!
If humans want to eat, they have to work.
I'll be a good girl and keep drawing maps.
Gather up 100 million berries.
Then bring it to me.
Do so and I will let your village go.
In addition to giving you your freedom.
Get that thief.
She's got our treasure.
Ever see just a kid?
I don't care, shoot her down.
Crap, find her. Run.
70 million only 70
million more will be free?
Oh so you made it back after all?
I guess you had nowhere else to go.
In that case, welcome back, navigator.
I'm sorry, you had a
truly horrific experience.
That's right, and she has you to think.
I did.
It was a nightmare.
Nothing will ever make me change
the way I feel about Arlong.
That said, until two years ago,
when we made the trip to Sabo Odi,
I had no idea that even the strongest of
fishmen were routinely
persecuted by humans.
When Kuma was kidnapped and we tried to
save her, I couldn't believe what I saw.
There was Sabo Odi Park,
right in front of me.
The spitting image of Arlong
Park before it was destroyed?
We wanted a
place all our own.
I'm not saying this to
make you forgive any of us!
But it's true.
Oh, Nami!
Arlong, he really hated humans.
Too much.
Yes, we went too far.
But for as long as I can remember,
we yearned for the world that the
humans lived in, above. the sea.
Arlong, me, all of us.
My people weren't considered anything
more than fish way back when.
Then,
200 years ago, the Ryugu Kingdom became
a member country of the world government.
They established friendly
relations with humans,
and their king was even allowed to
participate in the world's summit.
But, despite that, humans
still had hate in their hearts.
The beginning of the Great Pirate Era
was probably the worst time in my life.
It was hard to be a fish man.
I vividly remember my fear.
Human pirates running wild on the island.
Anywhere you went seemed dangerous.
So much violence.
I'll never forget.
Our only safe place in the
world was taken over by humans.
Then came that fateful day.
Whitebeard arrived on
the island and saved us.
He made his powerful presence felt,
claiming Fishman Island as his own.
Because of him, peace
returned to our home.
However, humans continue to
be prejudiced towards fishmen.
All of you saw it first hand
at the Sabo Odi Archipelago.
That's the cruel reality.
Naturally, once someone attains power,
they tend to be resisted to change.
Even though the government theoretically
bridged the gap between fishmen and humans,
the worst bigots were
the people in control to
begin with the ones who
should be leading by example
thus the relationship
between fish man and humans
remained the same
thankfully two individuals
rose up on fishman island individuals who
would help change the
course of our beleaguered
history the first was
queen otohime she believed
we islanders could live
in harmony with humans.
She was Princess Shirohoshi's mother.
Then there was him, the legendary
hero named Fisher Tiger,
who freed countless slaves.
That tiger guy, huh?
I think I've heard the name before.
To set himself apart from the humans,
Tiger broke an unspoken rule,
invading the holy land of Marie Joie by
himself and freeing the slaves within.
He would go on to form the Sun Pirates.
Many of its members were fishmen who
were formerly slaves of the nobles.
Sun Pirates? Indeed.
You know them as Arlong,
Hachi, and myself.
The three of us were part of the
very first crew of the Sun Pirates.
But we were known as Fishman Pirates,
foes of the world government.
That's all that they saw.
Therefore, we made it that much
more difficult for Queen Otohime.
Bless her heart, our existence
prevented much progress.
Queen Otohime was trying to navigate
great hardships and improve our future.
At the same time,
Fisher Tiger threw his future away to save
those of his race who
were suffering as slaves.
No one can say who was right or wrong.
Nevertheless, they both fought for a
better future for fishmen and humans.
Each one is a legend.
And both of their tales end in tragedy.